uploadingit.com 2008-12-16

# Tools - Uploadingit.com Free Image and File Hosting

Privacy Policy

**Overview**  
This privacy policy applies to the use of Uploadingit (http://www.uploadingit.com). Here at Uploadingit we take all our visitor's privacy very serious. We will never at any point sell or transfer personal identifiable information to other companies without the visitor's consent.

**Age**  
Uploadingit is a service not designed for users under the age of 13 (thirteen) years. If an underaged user is found using the service the user's account and any information of the user will be permanently terminated.

**Cookies and sessions**  
Cookies and sessions are data stored by your browser that contains various information that allow you to use Uploadingit's services to their fullest. Cookies and sessions do not contain personally identifiiable information. Cookies may also be used for demographic purposes and to track various visitor patterns accross Uploadingit.

Uploadingit allows some third-party advertisers that advertise on our website to store cookies onto your computer. Any cookies stored by advertising companies are not covered in Uploadingit's privacy policy. For more information please consult the privacy policy of such advertisers for more information.

Denying Uploadingit the ability to store cookies on your computer may cause certain parts of Uploadingit to not function correctly. We reccommend cookies are enabled to get the most out of Uploadingit's service.

We use various third parties to deliver adverts on Uploadingit. Some information about your visit to the site is used to determine which ads to show to you, no personal identifiable information of any form is stored.

**Information Collection**  
Uploadingit will only ever require personally identifiable information during registration. This information is used for demographic purposes and is shared with some advertisers in order to better target adverts towards you. These companies will never send you unsolicited email.

**IP Addresses**  
Your browser sends your IP address to any website in which you visit. Your IP address may be stored in various areas of Uploadingit's database(s) when registering or carrying out certain actions. Your IP address is stored to prevent mis-use of Uploadingit services and for demographical purposes.

**Information logged by Uploadingit.com**  
Your browser sends various information to all websites you visit, this includes Uploadingit. Such information includes your IP address, browser version and the page that refered you. This information is stored to prevent mis-use of Uploadingit services. All information submitted through forms throughout the website are also logged. Only authorized personnel have access to information stored in Uploadingit databases. Information where neccessary is also hashed or encrypted.

**Changes to this policy**  
Our policies are often reviewed and as such are subject to change. In the event of our policies being changed a notification will be displayed on the Uploadingit website.

**Contact Us**  
For any concerns relating to this privacy policy please send an email to us using this [contact form](http://uploadingit.com/contact).
